Resume
• Led the end-to-end design of the Availability Dashboard for company’s core internal platform, digitalizing the production
and management of weekly reports and successfully transitioning over 50% of internal teams to a unified workflow
• Supported transition to in-house billing for 450+ B2B customers, by re-designing invoices and consolidating B2B
customer data to a consolidated and integrated platform to reduce operational friction and ensure billing reliability
• Advanced branding initiatives by performing current brand evaluations through surveys and developing structured A/B
testing methods to gather actionable insights and feedback to inform customer driven decisions for company re-branding


• Managed all feature designs and prototypes for company’s B2C web and mobile app, consisting for 500+ active users
(free trial and paid users), informing decisions and driving effective solutions with user and competitive research insights
• Founded and led the user research team, scheduling and facilitating over 15+ user interviews, transformed and refined
the research process to tailor to company priorities, analyzed data to accelerate product and experience improvements
• Spearheaded the start-to-end design and product management of physical flashcard decks for AP course studying, to be
sold on Amazon, and oversaw the creation of all customer-facing materials to ensure consistent brand identity


• Lead design efforts by creating compelling user-centric design solutions and fostering seamless collaboration with developers.

• Shipped two projects (Penn Pins and Roomies) from ideation to development successfully, serving as product lead.

• Collaborated directly with the CEO to lead the redesign of a 1K+ user SaaS platform, improving usability, strengthening
brand coherence, and aligning with company’s mission of delivering a more efficient, customer-centric experience
• Conducted deep user and competitive research, guiding the redesign towards reducing friction and enhancing service

